Nicole Zheng

Front-end developer

with UX/UI focus

zznicole.does@gmail.com (+46) 733 805 392 https://www.linkedin.com/in/nicole-zheng-981a0a171/ https://github.com/zznicole

About

As a front-end developer with UX/UI focus, I'm passionate about web development, as well as enjoying taking on coding challenges, solving problems, and learning new things during each project.

With cross-industries experiences, I see each project from an idea to delivering to clients as a whole picture. Previously graduated and worked as Graphic Designer, which enabled me to have a good eye in the Visual, User Interface design. The study of User Experience design-related courses and years of experiences in hospitality, taught me how to emphasize our users' needs to ensure better user experiences. I'm a member of Interaction Design Foundation Linkoping.

Skills

Javascript, ES6, Vuejs, jQuery, Ajax, HTML5, CSS3, Git, Github, Bootstrap, Website optimization unit testing Jasmine, Low-High fidelity prototyping, Adobe XD, Figma, Photoshop, Illustrator, Design Teamwork, Empathy, Communication, Problem solving, Creativity, Self-motivated, Fast learning.

Experience

UX/UI intern

Cybercom Linkoping oct 2019- present

Founder & Designer

LoverNature Sweden sep 2018- present

Engaged in the visual content and UI design, UX analysis in Linkoping office with support from Stockholm office.

Worked on branding design, which included brands logo, colors, packaging, advertising flyers, as well as created eco-friendly products and social media updates.

Qantas Airways Sydney Australia may 2006--nov 2017

B/First Flight Attendant Responsible for passenger's inflight safety and Inquiries, enhancing customer inflight experience. Aircrafts worked on includes A380, A333, A332, B747, B767, B737. Throughout my tenure at Qantas Airways, I attended many training which involved analysing, prioritising, and solving CX related problems. Have been nominated 3 times to the Qantas eXcel award program for outstanding service.

Customer Service Supervisor Responsible for customer inquiries and resolving complaints.

Coles Group Sydney Australia 2003--2006

Graphic Designer

BESTA Group Shanghai China 2000--2001

Worked with the marketing team and sales team, designed brand'sl advertising on newspapers, and set up special indoor or outdoor events.

Graphic Designer

Converse Footwear Guangzhou China 1997--2000

Worked closely with the marketing department, designed advertising related posters, catalogs. I was also responsible for setting up events and designing graphics for Converse's products such as t-shirts, caps etc.

Education

PinkWebDev

PinkProgramming,Beetroot Academy Malmo 2020 Feb-Jun The 4 month front-end deveploment intensive course was organized by PinkProgramming, with support from Malmo Stad and powered by Beetroot Academy.

Human-Computer Interacton	Georgia Institute of Technology	Coursera	2019
Introduction to User Experience Design	Georgia Institute of Technology	Coursera	2019
Intro to the Design of Everyday things	By Don Norman	Udacity	2019
Fine Arts	Curtin University		11-2012 nesters)
Bachelor degree in Graphic Design	Wuhan Textile University	,	94-1997

Thank you for reading my resume.

Please feel free to contact me anytime on 0733 805 392 or zznicole.does@gmail.com